Hello,
Здравствуйте
I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky You’re from the
я из города Хмельницкий Вы откуда
North Caucasus Vladikavkaz Ossetian yes
Северный Кавказ Владикавказ осетин да О
What are you talking about
чем общаетесь
Yes not Just killing time a couple of hours have appeared
Да не Просто время убиваю появилось пару
Let’s go and have a look at the people Why do you
часов Давай зайду на людей посмотрю А
think Russia attacked
как думаете почему Россия напала на
Ukraine
Украину
Well, because some cards have developed
Ну потому что какие-то карты сложились
over the years, something  then there
на протяжении многих лет что-то там
were
происходило
maps and troops automatically begin to rush
карты и автоматически начинает набегать
in. But I’m
войска до Но я же
exaggerating how to explain
утрирую как бы объяснить
some events that took place
какие-то происходили события на
over many years without a clue I’m not a
протяжении многих лет без понятия не
politician I’m not in this anything you will support
политик я не в этом ничего вы поддержите
you opposite Ukraine the
вы напротив Украины
war as such
война как таковая
if you don’t know You’re not a politician  you don’t
если вы не знаете Вы не политик вы не
know maybe the politicians just took
знаете может политики просто взяли
Why is Russia a superpower a nuclear
Почему Россия сверхдержава ядерная
country and that I am one of the few
страна и что что я одна из немногих
for example India is a superpower
например Индия сверхдержава
India is a powerful country not a superpower
Индия могучая страна не сверхдержава
nuclear weapons is Israel is I am not
ядерное оружие это Израиль есть я не
outside of Israel
наружу Израиля
Well Israel So
Ну Израиль Так
only from nuclear weapons if you
что только от ядерного оружия если вы не
can’t use already  for a year and a half,
можете использовать уже полтора года
yours are dying and they hit you with a weapon. Well, they’re not
дохнут ваши и что ударили оружием Ну не
dying, but yours are dying. It’s
дохнут а погибают
all just because your
ваши дохнут Все просто потому что ваша
occupiers protect ours with such negativity.
оккупанты наши защищает негатив такой
Why, when we killed the Germans in the Second World War,
Почему когда мы во Вторую мировую войну
the Germans died, and ours
убивал немцев немцы дохли А наши типа
died, I think every warrior treats the
умирали Я думаю каждый воин относится к
enemy with some respect
врагу С неким уважением
Is it possible with those who
можно с тем кто
attacked without declaring war
напал без объявления войны
brazenly at night to
нагло ночью
respect the orcs who are
уважать орков которые
not there
нет
wait stop stop then Ossetians live in Ukraine
подожди стоп стоп то осетин в Украине
Ossetians I
живут осетины
don’t know live whales That is, it turns out
не знаю живут кита То есть получается
look if there is Asi you are Ossetian Yes in
смотри если есть Аси ты осетин Да в
Ossetia and you positive ones are going to fight
Осетии и вас позитивные идут воевать
in Ukraine So what did they do  Ossetians
в Украину Так причем что делали осетином
Ukrainians
украинцы
I don’t understand your questions at all What are
Я вообще не понимаю ваших вопросов Что
we Ossetians Russians Well look
такое мы осетины россияне Ну смотри
okay let me explain this way
хорошо давай так давай так объясню
Look, for example, you slaughtered Ossetians
Смотри вот вы например осетины вырезали
in a suburban area of ​​the Ingush, Ukrainians
в пригородном районе ингушей украинцы
did something bad to you
что-то делали с вами плохого
Yes, I don’t understand at all why this conversation
Да вообще не пойму к чему этот разговор
Ossetians slaughtered and expelled  Ingush
осетины вырезали изгнали ингушей
remember
помните
Yes, the Ukrainians
Да украинцы
did something bad to you
что-то вам плохого сделали
I remember the Ukrainian
Я помню украинский
[music]
[музыка]
in the Chechen war the
в Чеченской войне
Ukrainians did something to you networks
вам что-то сети нам сделали украинцы
I personally don’t So why are your
мне лично нет Так почему вот ваша
Ossetians, for example, fighting in Ukraine against
осетины например воюют в Украине против
Ukraine Well, I’m only speaking for myself, I’m not
Украины Ну я говорю только за себя я не
Well  here is your network, that is, they turn out to be
Ну вот ваша сети то есть они получается
traitors to their people, they are going in short
предатели своего народа они едут короче
for someone, the Tsar of Moscow, like killing
за кого-то Московского царя типа убивать
people in another country. No, this is the
людей в другой стране Да нет это
President of the Russian Federation,
Президент Российской Федерации
look again, the President of the Russian
смотрите еще раз президент Российской
Federation took the Ossetians. Yes, for example, there are
Федерации взял осетин Да например там
Bashkorts there and then sent them to Ukraine to kill
башкорт и тогда послал в Украину убивать
people  the
людей
name itself Yes, that’s why it’s called
само название Да поэтому называется
Bashkortostan, before it was Bashkiria,
Башкортостан раньше было Башкирия
they renamed Bashkortostan
переименовали Башкортостан
Once again, what happened in Ukraine, that
Еще раз что случилось в Украине что
Russia is taking Buryats,
Россия берет бурят
Ossetians, Chechens,
осетин чеченцев
not to die, but to defend Well,
не подыхать а защищать
probably everyone has some
Ну наверное каждый есть какие-то
interests I’m not a politician Why why
интересы Я же не политик Почему почему
he Look every
он Смотри каждый
time Look Such global topics are
раз Смотри Такие глобальные темы
global  a person is
глобальные человек
being thrown, look, a person is being thrown to die in
кидают смотри человека кидает умереть в
another country, yes, and why he
другую страну да А за что он не понимает
doesn’t understand, no one for some reason understands the interests of
никто почему-то не понимает интересы
states.
государств
Well, who cares
Ну какая разница
what the purpose should be, a special
какая должна быть цель специальная
operation, what Putin said is interesting, the
операция что Путин сказал интересный
state is protected, we all know perfectly well,
государство защищены Все мы прекрасно
I won’t be with you
все знаете я же не буду вам
Every Ossetian has his own version, so
у каждого осетина своя версия есть вот у
you have
вас какая
my version, that I don’t stick my
у меня такая версия что я не сую свой
nose in, as well as the fact that I don’t understand anything in
нос как и то что я ничего не понимаю в
this understanding. I don’t even want to
этом понимании Я не хочу Даже это
discuss this. Wait, they stuck it out, you already
обсуждать Подождите высунули уже вы
said that yes, like, This corresponds to
сказали что да типа Это соответствует
the interests of the country. Well,  How do you not
интересам страны Ну а как вы не
understand what kind of interest there is? No, I don’t
понимаете какие там интерес Нет не
understand, I have my own little life,
понимаю у меня есть своя маленькая жизнь
when trouble touches me, I or
когда меня коснется беда я или меня
someone asks me for something, and if tomorrow they
кто-то там что-то попросит а если завтра
announce mobilization, they take you
у вас объявляет мобилизацию вас забирает
to Ukraine, you will go to fight, but they won’t
в Украину вы пойдете воевать но у нас не
announce it here  mobilization Why that we
объявят мобилизации Почему что у нас
have a lot of mercenaries who are fresh
много есть наемников которые свежачок
now, straight fresh
сейчас прям свеженькая
So that means the
Так значит
general is a map of the floors, he is now a
генерал карта полов он сейчас депутат
State Duma deputy who was not just a map,
Госдумы дачи кто не просто карта была
so he writes the first mobilized
вот он пишет первый мобилизированный
Russians to leave the combat zone
россияне покинуть зону боевых действий
after the end of a special military
после окончания специальной военной
operation on the territory of Ukraine, that is,
операции на территории Украины то есть
they will return  home after the completion of a
они вернутся домой после завершения
special operation, no rotation is
специальной операции ротация никакая не
provided for, they are entitled to leave every 6
предусмотрена им положен отпуск каждый 6
further also yesterday Sobolev is a
дальше также вчера Соболев депутат
State Duma deputy, so
Госдумы так вот
I quote today’s statement by
цитирую сегодняшнее заявление депутатов
Sobolev’s deputies on simplifying the
Соболева об упрощении требований к
health requirements for conscripts is considered
здоровью призывников считается
categorically unacceptable not these
Категорически неприемлемый не этими
inconsistencies with the status of a people’s What
несоответствие статусу народный Что
happened that your deputy Sobolev
случилось что ваш депутат Соболев да
says that  it is necessary to ease the
говорит что нужно так облегчить
requirements for military service so that you can
требования к воинской службе что можно
take sick people there You know what a
там больных брать Вы знаете что должен
deputy should do what
делать депутат что
but he must come up with laws amendments
но он должен придумывать законы поправки
Why it turns out look he put forward
Почему получается смотрите он выдвинул
something like this yes What happened that
вот такой вот да Что случилось такое Что
she already works for a deputy yes Well what
депутату она уже работает да Ну что
happened that What a deputy has to
случилось такое Что депутату приходится
think about how to make it so that the
задумываться как бы сделать так чтобы
sick can be taken to the front, which is
больных можно было взять на фронт что
so, well, the deputy needs to sit and
так ну депутату надо сидеть деньги свои
work off his money, he must
отрабатывать он должен какую-нибудь
come up with some kind of thing, the fact that we had a
штуку придумывать то что у нас была
mobilization of 300 thousand people there
мобилизация там 300 тысяч человек
last year,
прошлом году правильно
that’s right, how do you know that 300 they are 400 Well, I
откуда вы знаете что 300 они 400 Ну я
I know that this year, how do you know, you were
знаю что в этом году откуда вы знаете вы
n’t interested in politics? That’s how
с политика не интересовались Вот откуда
you knew that 300, they needed half a million, they
вы знали что 300 они полмиллиона надо
needed 300, I
было 300
read, I heard how many
прочитал услышал сколько живых осталось
of these 300 mobilized were alive, I can’t
из этих 300 мобилизированных я не могу
say because I’m incompetent in
сказать потому что я некомпетентен в
this matter, I know, in short, I didn’t understand  I’ll
этом вопросе Я знаю короче не понял
call you that, you know, incompetent You
я вас так назову знаете некомпетяжка Вы
when necessary I’m incompetent when you say something like that as a
когда надо я некомпетентный когда так
deputy I’m not a Captain I’ll
что-то говорите депутатом я не Капитан я
tell you how many volunteers have been called up
вам скажу сколько призвано Добровольцев
This year about
в этом году около
80 thousand
80 тысяч
look And how many soldiers do you have in Ukraine
смотрите А сколько у вас в Украине
380 thousand Volunteers 300
солдат 380 тысяч Добровольцев 300
mobilized How many cadre army do
мобилизированных Кадровая армия сколько
you have  there’s a soldier in Ukraine Yes, I have no
у вас же в Украине солдат Да я без
idea, it’s cool, it’s already a million,
понятия прикольно уже получается миллион
no, someone quits from the first company
нет кто-то же с первой компании
Well, after such words, it’s not very nice to be
Ну вот после таких слов не очень приятно
with you Here’s
с вами
a video when our Ukrainians ask,
Вот видео когда наши украинцы спрашивают
but I don’t Well, it was good 300 thousand
но я не Ну хорошо было 300 тысяч
mobilized, you said 380 thousand
мобилизированных вы сказали 380 тысяч
volunteers, too, 680 thousand personnel
добровольца тоже 680 тысяч кадровой
army was still there under a million where all
армии еще было там под миллион где все
these people
эти люди
someone is returning home there is no such
кто-то домой возвращается нет такой
probability how many returned home the one
вероятности сколько вернулась домой тот
who has already served, yes, what an honor I will say
кто отслужил уже да я что почёт я скажу
I’m leading We have how many returned, I’ll
я веду У нас есть сколько вернулась я
tell you how many returned home by
вам скажу сколько вернулась домой по
According to the Ukrainian Gestab,
данным украинского гештаба домой
271,790 Russians returned home, but there
271790 россиян но сколько
is one nuance, there is one nuance, these
есть один нюансы есть один нюанс эти
Russians actually returned dead,
россияне вернулись дохлыми
some are in black bags,
реально кто-то в пакетах черных кто-то
some are just loaded there, some don’t
просто там нагружены некоторые вообще не
take you at all, in reality, even in front of the children, they
забирает вот реально вас даже при детях
sing this song in the shopping center.
поют в торговом центре вот эту песню
our children are weaving nets
У нас дети плетут сетки
at school right now on
в школе вот сейчас
September 1st
1 сентября
why they set it up at school
почему в школе поставили
children come out
дети выходят
Well and then you create questions why is it
Ну а потом вы создаете вопросы почему
normal for children children Russia is bombing the
нормально ли дети дети Россия бомбит в
country then children should sit in a bomb shelter
страну тогда дети должны в бомбоубежище
yes of course they want to kill you
сидеть да конечно они хотят убить вас
all this is normal even your president
всех это нормально даже ваш президент
said  that these children will have bombs, you're running,
говорил что эти дети будут бомбы бежишь
come on, show me, show me this phrase
давай покажи покажи эту фразу
you were there Show me this phrase in full show
ты был вот Покажи эту фразу полностью
it's okay what he said that Russia
Да ничего что он сказал что Россия
will come Yes and there will be a war and then there will be
придет Да и будет война и тогда будут
a bomb shelter That's what he said Because
бомбоубежище Вот что он сказал Потому
you were
что ты был
Show me this phrase in full Show
Покажи мне эту фразу полностью Покажи
me  really
ты реально
they killed as many in the suburban
вели поубивали столько пригородном
area as you live on their lands their
районе сколько живете на их землях их
houses now Yes, really, you’re trying
домах сейчас Да правда вы пытаетесь
How many children were killed, they
Сколько было убито детей
took them for children, well, look,
то за детей взяли ну да смотри вот
look, it’s so
смотри так
funny, man, I don’t know I open
смешно человек я не знаю Я открываю
Wikipedia Yes, it’s even
Википедию Да даже разговаривать
unpleasant to talk, but why
неприятно но почему
Well, because it’s unpleasant  man, what
Ну потому что неприятный человек а что
happened, look Ossetians
случилось смотри осетины
Yes, with the support of the Russian army Yes,
Да вот при поддержке российской армии Да
you expelled the Ingush from their
вы изгнали ингушей из своих земель
historical lands on which the lands of their
исторических на которых земли их
great-grandfathers
прадедов
were settled all their lives
всю жизнь своя заселились
[music]
[музыка]
killed Yes, and settled.
убивали Да и заселились
Look
Вот смотри
where he ran from October 30 to November 4, 1992
куда убежал с 30 октября по 4 ноября 92
Go online  against the Ingush, with the
года Зайдите сети на ингушки при
support of the Russian troops,
поддержке российских войск
407 Ingush died according to official
вот погибло 407 ингушей по официальным
data,
данным
and right away I was on fire, this is a sore point for them,
а сразу я подгорел это больной для них
subscribe to us, a kilogram right at a time,
подпишись нами килограмм прям за раз
autumn, and the ass is
осень а попок
more and more important YouTube, driving
ц дуже и дуже важнева YouTube загоняя
us through the cardioreck into a shadow ban and the
нас через кардиорке в теневый бан и
video is too much not shown to people  in
дужебовато видео не показывается людям в
private, information about
частном на показывается информация про
streams is shown in order for the little
стримы тому для того чтобы мало
operational little animal Sign right at a
оперативный зверезок Подпишите прям за
time and the butt is there in a kilogram about Cream
раз а попок там в килограмме о Крим
video
видео
information and we will
информация и мы с вами
show you
покажем вам
[music]
[музыка]